this is software engineering radio the
podcast for professional developers on
the web at sc-radio.net
c-radio is brought to you by the IEEE
computer Society IEEE software Magazine
online at computer.org software
hello and welcome to software
engineering radio
I'm your host nickel and in today's
software engineering radio episode we
welcome Gregory kapfhama an associate
professor at Allegheny College with a
PhD from the University of Pittsburgh
his research focuses on software
engineering and testing particularly on
flaky tests Gregory is involved in
various academic roles including
associate editor program Committee
Member and reviewer he also contributes
to open source software testing and
Analysis tools on GitHub
our discussion will center around the
common problem of flaky tests
encountered in software development
so welcome to the show Gregory and was
there anything in the bio that you might
want to add that I am asked
first of all let me say thank you for
inviting me to chat today about flaky
tests I'm excited to be a guest on
software engineering radio and I think
everything that you shared was wonderful
let's dive into the conversation great
let's start with the basics right so
what is a flaky test and why as a
software developer should I care about
flaky tests so a flaky test is a test
case that passes or fails even when you
don't change the source code of the
program under test or the test Suite
itself
this is a real challenge for software
developers because the quality of the
test case signal is diminished this
means that a test might pass sometimes
and then fails sometimes and the
developer won't be able to know whether
the failures actually indicate that
there's a bug in the program that they
need to resolve that sounds kind of
annoying obviously that's that's not
great right so what exactly does it kind
of hinder right so obviously one is
basically it's not great to have a test
that sometimes starts and fails but are
there any other process driven things
that might get impacted yeah that's a
really good point so when you have a
flaky test in your test Suite it often
hinders continuous integration and
continuous development so you might have
a build that fails in continuous
integration and you wonder why it fails
and you also wonder why it sometimes
passes and sometimes fails so if that's
due to a flaky test then it causes you
as a developer to stop trusting the CI
and CD environment and therefore limits
your ability to add new features or to
introduce bug fixes
yeah that sounds like something that I
would do as well if I had a CI CD
environment that's flaky and there's
something to be delivered and like oh
yeah it fails half the time I'm gonna
I'm gonna just throw the dice as they
say maybe we can talk about a real world
example that you might have encountered
where this is common yeah that's a
really good question so I myself have
implemented a number of software testing
or automated assessment tools that I
have released to GitHub one of the tools
that I have built is an automated
assessment tool that I use when I am
checking my students work there were
some order dependent test cases within
that test suite and so if I ran the
tests in a different order than the
standard order the test cases would
sometimes fail in a flaky fashion this
made it really difficult for me as a
developer to know whether or not the new
feature that I had added was correct
and the test case was failing in a flaky
fashion or there was actually a real bug
inside of my program right I mean I'm
sure you must have given your student a
year full
about that so okay so you talked about
order dependent and non-order dependent
so is that a way to categorize flaky
tests as order dependent or not and
maybe you could give us some examples of
what a non-order dependent if you if you
can
yeah that's a great point so first let
me say that an order dependent flaky
test case is a test case that tends to
pass and fail in a flaky fashion when
you run it in a different order than
which it was originally intended to be
run this often happens in a regression
testing environment when you only want
to run a subset of test cases on your
developer laptop or in CI
another kind of flaky test case is
called a non-order dependent flaky test
these are test cases that pass and fail
in a flaky fashion for reasons not
connected to order
so they could be related to timing
issues they could be related to
asynchronous issues or networking issues
or maybe issues that are related to the
CPU or the memory or the file system
those non-order dependent flaky tests
are also critical to limiting our
confidence in the correctness of the
program and the test Suite right it
sounds like the non-order dependent ones
would be also harder to debug right
because with the auto dependent one it's
kind of easy to say okay find this if
you change the order it fails and if you
keep a particular order it's the same so
you talked about CPU and memory and all
that and kind of led me to this
particular thought so what are the
common sources of flaky tests that are
related to the external environment for
example what are some of the other
common sources that we have yeah your
mentioned about the CPU and the memory
is a really good one so in my experience
both in my own test Suites and in the
real world ones that we've examined on
GitHub projects we have found that if
the CPU changes significantly that is
for example it goes to being a slower
CPU model
or the memory changes significantly for
example much less memory is available
test Suites tend to become more flaky in
nature that's because of the fact that
you often might have certain resource
constraints in mind as an assumption
when you're writing the test case as a
developer and then those assumptions can
be violated when you're running it in a
different execution environment that has
like for example a different class of
CPU or a different amount of memory
great so so those are obviously some
physical sources do you think they may
be actual problems in your program that
might lead to a flaky test that's a
really good point in my experience it
has both been a problem in my test suite
and also a problem in my program for
example there have been cases when I was
building applications that had a
significant web user interface and for
those systems sometimes my test cases
were flaky because parts of the web user
interface didn't appear fast enough or
According to some timeline that was
expected by the test case in that
situation it was really a problem in my
program that manifested itself as a
flaky test right so it's kind of like a
performance issue in the way you render
your web interface for example that that
might be kind of causing this okay what
about other things do you think like
there could be a time related factor in
this because I've noticed that
I I at least when I do my tests I always
get nervous when it comes to time
because you have different time zones
you can run servers in different places
Etc right so what are your experiences
with time or what do you think that
that's a that that is something that we
should uh be careful about
so as a developer modeling and correctly
handling the date and the time is in my
experience one of the most challenging
things to do correctly
so there may be situations in which the
test cases pass if they're run in a
certain time zone or if they're run at a
certain time of day but if assumptions
about the test cases date or time or the
program's date or time or violated then
the test case may start to fail in a
flaky fashion
so I would say it's not only issues
about timing
that is how long it takes for things to
appear in the UI or to run in an
asynchronous fashion but it's also about
the date and the time modeled from the
perspective of both the program and the
test Suite
right right just to share a real world
use case from from my work I work in a
in the logistics space so for me for us
basically time zones is a major deal
right because you're moving cargo across
the world and there have been more than
one occasion where literally a test
would be running in my time zone and
then we deploy it to the cluster and the
cluster happens to be in America and
suddenly all the tests failed because
the flights that were supposed to start
or the tests that had assumed uh the
flight would start on a particular date
has now suddenly shifted to the previous
day right so uh this is this has been my
experience at least with flaky tests so
obviously there are these carbon sources
so how how can we detect this is there a
way that we can actually before we have
to go and send it to the CI CD and
before we actually committed to the git
repositories is there a way for us to
figure out that okay these these tests
might be flaky even before we do that I
mean come in yeah I think that there are
a number of things that developers can
do to detect that a test case is flaky
one of the things that I normally first
do is re-run a test case some fixed
number of times so if the test case
tends to pass or fail in a
non-deterministic fashion then I often
will first run that test case in
isolation a repeated number of times
if it passes in isolation a repeated
number of times then I might start to
gradually increase how many test cases I
run and the context in which I run those
test cases and then continue to re-run
it a fixed number of times
to give a concrete example let's say
that I have two test cases that are
interacting inadvertently through shared
state in a database or in a file system
what I might then be able to discover is
that when I re-run those test cases
together as a pair or as a group they
negatively influence each other and
cause flakiness
in that case to solve the problem I
would try to introduce better set up and
tear down methods for those test cases
and then help to ensure that they're no
longer flaky when I run them both in
isolation and additionally in a group of
other tests right I mean that's that I
guess is one way of doing it it also
speaks to you should probably make your
test fast because if you want to run it
on multiple times like this then
definitely that's that's something that
you should consider are there any tools
that we can use kind of like a linting
tool or some kind of statistical
analysis that we can do maybe to figure
out if a test might be flaky yeah that's
a really good question the first thing I
should say before I get to your comment
about statistical analysis is that often
I use tools that help me to do an
automated re-running as soon as the test
case is detected as flaky
so that way I don't have to do any
manual re-running on my own I just allow
my testing framework to re-run the test
cases for me
I also use tools both for Java
programming and for Python Programming
that can attach markers to my test cases
I could have a flaky marker that
automatically appears on a test if
re-running indicates that it's likely to
be flaky
then I can change my re-running process
so that at least for a period of time it
screens out those test cases that are
the flaky ones running the rest of the
test suite and then allowing me to focus
back on maybe finding and fixing the
sources of flakiness in the test cases
that were automatically marked as being
flaky oh okay cool so these would be
Frameworks that you run on top of the
actual unit testing framework that you
have right yeah that's exactly right
okay so the the now we've detected a
flaky test then what what should we do
now how do we actually tackle this
particular test what is the approach
that we do one of the things that I do
at this point is investigate how the
test case is interacting with the
execution environment so for example I
might introduce instrumentation into
either my program or my test Suite that
instrumentation can do things like track
how the test interacts with the file
system or track how the program
interacts with the file system I can
also track other things like code
coverage memory usage and execution time
one of the things that I found is that
if a test case takes up too much memory
or repeatedly accesses the file system
in a way I didn't predict that that
might be an indicator as to why it is
flaky right when you say instrumentation
is to clarify you're talking about
things like logging or adding metrics
that you can and measurements about on
your code or do you have like a specific
instrumentation Tooling in mind that's a
really good point so when it comes to
instrumentation you can as a developer
introduce that into your system on your
own or alternatively you can use a wide
variety of Open Source and or commercial
tools that can monitor the execution of
your program and your test Suite as a
concrete example of that there is a
product called datadog and datadog can
monitor both the behavior of your
program and the test suite and then give
you hints that will help you to discover
why your test case may be flaky ah okay
that is cool okay so we have looked at
it and we've kind of instrumented it
should we even repair it can we just
delete this test I mean how do we
actually make the call whether you
should spend your time because after all
it is a test you're not actually
delivering features here right you're
not you're not delivering business value
so one argument could be made is that
hey you can't spend that much time on
the test just delete the test so how do
you actually make that kind of
determination let's say about this yeah
that's a good point so there are two
things that I would say in response
first one of the things that I often do
is quarantine the test case and stop
running it in continuous integration as
I mentioned previously another thing
that I'll sometimes do is Mark the test
case as a flaky test and then I will
skip it for a period of time
however if I quarantine a test case or
skip a test case I may be missing out on
the fault detecting potential that is
associated with that test
another point that I would briefly add
is that sometimes there's a silver
lining to flaky test cases sometimes
test cases that are flaky are actually
pointing out a problem in the business
logic of my program and so it might be
helpful to me in certain circumstances
to at least invest some time to root
causing the flaky test because it could
lead me to actually finding a bug in my
program oh awesome so that's great I
mean this is another example why I love
testing because even a bad test can give
you more information than no testing at
all right that's great so okay I've
decided to track down this particular
flaky test and try to see if I can
repair it how would I go about doing
that should I I like you said quarantine
the test but that's basically
essentially skipping it do you think
it'll be better to maybe look at the
setup and tear down functions or try to
see if we can make sure that this test
is well factored or isolated better than
currently what you're suggesting is
something that I definitely try to do
especially if I'm dealing with an order
dependent flaky test case I will often
try to make sure that I have the best
possible setup and tear down methods
associated with all my tests especially
those test cases that are flaky
obviously there's a trade-off here when
it comes to the flakiness of my test
suite and the performance of the overall
testing process
so one of the trade-offs that I have
personally experienced is that if I
clear out a significant amount of state
from a database or a file system or
things that are shared in memory that
could cause my test Suite to run more
slowly than it would otherwise because
I'm executing a lot of heavyweight code
in either setup or tear down
so ultimately I want to try to find the
right balance between clearing out
enough of the shared state so that I
don't have flakiness but maybe allowing
some shared State as long as it doesn't
negatively influence the outcomes of
test cases
okay so what happens what would you do
if you actually went down this
particular route and at the end of the
day you found that okay this is
something that's maybe a little bit
beyond your control right so it might be
that okay there is a network problem
between your machine or your laptop and
the the server on which the test is
trying to connect to a third-party
service that you can't mock out and
basically that is kind of causing this
do you think there is actual value in
still retaining the test but not
actually running it that often more kind
of like from uh maybe don't call don't
use it as a unit test but use it as a
integration test or a smoke a smoke test
or something that you run less often but
just to make sure that things are
working do you think there's value in
that wow that's a great point before I
directly answer your question let me
pick up on something you said a moment
ago one of the things that I tried to do
which you talked about is the idea of
introducing various kinds of mock
objects or mock Services into my test
Suite the idea there is that instead of
interacting with some unpredictable
third-party service I'll actually have a
mark of that third party service and in
my experience that often helps me to
control flakiness of course at the
expense of perhaps limiting the realism
of the test cases that I'm running right
and in some cases that that might be the
even point of the test right you might
have written the test to kind of
exercise that part of the functionality
so that's that's kind of like so if you
kind of like driven up the wall down
that situation then what what do you
recommend that we do yeah so now we come
to the question of if we can can't have
mocks but we recognize there's flakiness
perhaps because of our dependence on
some third-party API then in that
situation I think we should do precisely
what you suggested a moment ago which is
to make those test cases run
infrequently like maybe they're part of
an integration test Suite or maybe
they're part of a smoke test Suite but
the idea is maybe we don't run them
frequently inside a CI but we run them
as a separate process perhaps right
before we make a major release or when
we're introducing a big feature to our
system
great point and I also actually want to
Circle back a little bit on a point that
you've made earlier regarding you know
certain a class of tests which are the
UI tests let's let's say right the web
UI the web tests and and you mentioned
that they tend to be more there tend to
be more cases of flaky tests amongst
them so can you maybe talk a little
about why that is and if you have any
recommendations to kind of optimize that
as much as possible you can reduce that
flakiness
so in my experience when I'm building
test cases for web user interfaces or
graphical user interfaces sometimes my
test cases are flaky because of the fact
that there are timing constraints in the
user interface and my test case may make
an assumption about how quickly
something appears in the web UI or in
the graphical user interface so in those
situations I try to make my test cases
more event driven in nature as opposed
to making them timing or weight based in
nature
another thing that I have found super
helpful especially when I'm dealing with
web user interfaces or mobile apps is
avoiding hard coding my test cases for
the user interface to individual pixels
or individual locations I want to make
them more about existing widgets in the
web user interface or in the Android app
and less about their precise location on
the screen because that often introduces
flakiness which I think can be avoided
if you adopt one of the strategies I
mentioned
right so so just to kind of make sure
that I understood so what you're
recommending is that a don't kind of
introduce timing based tests basically
try to look for a listen for events that
have happened and then basically write
your tests around okay this event
happened therefore this must have this
test has passed or or not right and the
other one was regarding making it a
little less brittle by looking for the
existence of certain components or
features in the UI rather than uh
looking at it from a pixel based or a
point based placing it in the layout so
to speak excellent suggestions have you
thought about also so so when you look
at the event based thing right one of
the things also is that the event might
not happen right so that that might be
because your code is wrong right so your
test is waiting for an event but the
event might not appear because you know
wrote something your business logic
broke right so how how do you actually
deal let's say does your test basically
wait for that event for a certain amount
of time and then give up or how do you
actually write that test yeah that's a
good point and it makes me think of two
things in particular so first of all we
know that we can't wait for an
indefinite period of time
so in that situation we still ultimately
do have to introduce some type of
timeouts but we try to make the timeout
big enough so that the event will always
occur within a reasonable period of time
the other thing in response to your
point that I have found helpful for both
graphical user interfaces or web
interfaces or code-based testing is to
think carefully about the oracles or the
assertions that are inside my tests if
my Oracle is looking at too much of the
state
whether that's the UI or the database or
the file system it may be waiting for
events to happen or content to appear
but that's not really critical for the
test cases assertions to be able to pass
so another strategy that I've adopted is
thinking very carefully about the
oracles or the assertions and ensuring
that they're narrow enough so that they
don't become flaky right just to kind of
Enlighten myself what do you mean when
you say Oracle can you kind of explain
that term to me
so the Oracle is the part of the test
case that helps us to know whether the
test case did or did not pass
so if we're taking a simple example the
idea of the Oracle is to accept the
output that comes back from the function
under test and then to inspect all or
some portion of that output
if what you're looking for appears in
the output then the Oracle or we could
say the assertion will allow the test
case to pass but if the Oracle looks in
the output and it says hey I can't find
what I'm looking for then in that
situation exactly the test case would
fail Okay Okay cool so I'm used to the
term assertions for that so this is this
is today I learned thanks for thanks for
enlightening me so moving on obviously
you had mentioned uh there were tools
that we could use to detect flaky tests
and maybe even handle aspects of flaky
tests can you kind of talk about do you
know of any tools or can you recommend a
few tools that in Java and python
because those are the ones languages
that you mentioned you did your research
on that that you can use for flaky tests
so the first thing that I would say is
that there are many tools for both
Python and Java developers that allow
you to do various types of intelligent
re-running of your test Suite normally
these are plugins to a specific test
automation framework or some type of
build system
for example the maven build system has
the Surefire plugin that will do
re-running of your test Suite when a
flaky test case is detected
there are similar plugins that you can
use if you're a python developer and you
are using pi test as your testing
framework for both of those tools I
would say that re-running is one of the
easiest and nicest places to start when
it comes to leveraging tools that will
help you to detect and or fix flaky
tests
the other area is a bigger area that we
may want to investigate in Greater
detail and that is the use of tools that
use machine learning in order to help
you to find and fix flaky test cases
right that that sounds fascinating and
machine learning is quite the fashion
right now can you elaborate a little bit
more on how how that can be done so when
it comes to machine learning the first
thing that we should talk about is
whether we're using a supervised or
unsupervised or reinforcement machine
learning technique
my specific examples and the tools that
we've built and released on GitHub all
use what are called supervised machine
learning algorithms the idea there is
that you're going to collect information
about the program and the test suite and
then you're going to connect that with
information about whether the test case
is or is not flaky and then use a
trained machine learning model to make
predictions about the flakiness of test
cases in your system
okay cool but a man and this is just me
being a complete uh novice in this I'm
not a that familiar with machine
learning techniques but my understanding
is that machine learning for the large
part is a probabilistic method right so
if you apply a machine learning
technique they can at the most tell you
probabilistically that this is this is
probably the solution that you're
looking for how do you actually deal
with that is that the method that you
used which is a supervised machine
learning method you get better results
from that and you know I'm more
confident about your results there
that's a good point so let me address it
in part and then I'll turn it back over
to you for further clarification and
question
the first thing that I would say is that
you have to have some information about
both the program and the test suite and
the better information you have the
better the machine learning algorithm is
going to be able to make predictions
the features that you're going to
collect are what I would call static
features and dynamic features
the static features are those that you
can extract by looking at the source
code of the program and the test Suite
the dynamic features are those that you
can extract by actually running and
observing the program and the test suite
and again my first main point is the
better features you have the better the
machine learning algorithm is going to
be able to do
at predicting the individual test cases
and whether or not they're going to be
flaky right so when you when you say
features could you give us some examples
of this is it like a is it like the
number of commits is it the users is it
any aspects of the code is it metadata
about the code what kind of features are
you talking about
so when it comes to a static feature
some of the things that we might extract
are related to what's known as the
abstract syntax tree or the AST of
either the program or the test Suite the
idea might be the more complicated or
deep that is the abstract syntax tree
then maybe the more likely that it is
going to ultimately manifest in
flakiness that would be again an example
of what we would call a static feature a
concrete example of a dynamic feature
might be things like the memory overhead
of a test case the utilization of the
file system on behalf of the test or
maybe additional information about the
code coverage associated with running
the test Suite on a system under test
right okay and what you're saying is
that with the combination of these
features your machine learning then
program then builds a model that can
predict with a reasonable amount of
accuracy areas of the program or areas
of the tests which are flaking
yeah so the idea is that's exactly right
so the idea is you collect all of these
features and then for every test Suite
you run for every test you run the test
case repeatedly in isolation and then
you notice that there's flakiness then
that would suggest to you it's very
likely a non-order dependent flaky test
then if you rerun the test Suite in
groups or the test Suite as a whole and
you find certain test cases are flaky
then that's an indicator that they're
likely to be order dependent flaky tests
those then are the labels that you would
feed into the machine learning algorithm
so you give it information about a test
behavior and its static structure you
give it information about the program's
behavior and its static structure then
for every test you give it the label
from re-running which would indicate
whether the test case is flaky or is not
flaky you then train a model like for
example a neural network or a random
forest or other kinds of machine
learning algorithms and then you can use
that trained model to make predictions
about new test cases or revisions to
test cases as they come into your test
Suite cool that sounds really cool and
thank you for going into that because
this is a this is this was new and I
never thought about machine learning as
as a way to kind of look at improving
flaky tests
let's move into a little bit further
different slightly different topic which
is obviously we have tooling that
handles flaky tests after they've
happened and we have now tooling you
talked about where it can help you
predict maybe flaky test coming up but
how can developers avoid the
introduction of flaky tests in the first
place are there any practices or
processes they can follow to help them
make sure that they're not writing
flicky tests
one of the things that I tried to
initially do to avoid introducing flaky
test cases is always run my test Suite
in a random order when I'm doing
development on my laptop I also add
something into my CI configuration so
that in CI I also run my test Suite in a
random order
both of those strategies are super
helpful when it comes to avoiding the
introduction of order dependent flaky
test cases inside of my test Suite okay
so obviously running the test Suite in a
random order is probably tooling to do
that as well right you don't have to
actually
consciously run them in a random order
that's right yeah I often use tools that
will automatically rerun the test Suite
in a random order so for example there
are several tools that integrate with
the python
testing tool called Pi test and it will
allow you to rerun the test Suite in
random orders and you can do that again
as I said before both on your
development laptop and in continuous
integration
okay are there anything that we can do
in the writing of tests as a kind of
like a practices we can do when writing
tests to avoid writing flaky tests
one of the things that I try to do is to
ensure that I write simple test cases
that are easy to understand
so a goal that I set for myself whenever
possible is to avoid introducing
conditional logic or Loops into my test
Suite so when I'm writing a test Suite
in junit or Pi test or another unit
testing framework if I'm introducing
Loops or conditional logic and then
putting assertions inside of those
constructs to me that's a warning sign
that maybe my test case could become
flaky if different conditional paths or
execution structures are taken when I'm
running the test Suite
whenever it's possible to do so I also
try to ensure that I have as few
assertions as possible in my test Suite
because that will also give me more
confidence in the test cases reliability
when it's run frequently on a developer
workstation or in CI okay okay so
Simplicity and a single responsibility
so as few assertions as possible can we
kind of write tests that are very
focused is there something we can do in
our the way we write programs so write
our actual program to make it less
susceptible to flaky tests maybe we
could write something that is easier to
test in somehow in some way to kind of
help with that there's one strategy that
I always think of to Aid my testing
process and it has to do with the number
of inputs that go into the function
under test and then the number of
outputs so if I have a function that
accepts a significant number of inputs
but only a single output or no outputs
then I probably don't have enough
visibility and so therefore the test
Suite might not be able to run in a
fashion to ensure the correctness of the
program
so partly it's about ensuring that my
functions in the program under test have
a sufficient amount of visibility so
that I can ensure that they're working
correctly
another thing is connected to what you
said a moment ago just like test cases
need to have a single Focus I try to
ensure that the components or functions
in my system also have a single Focus
because that makes them easier to test
as well yeah so I think that's that's a
good amount of practical advice and
thanks Gregory for doing that and yeah I
mean I think this is uh this has been a
a good episode do you have anything in
mind that we did not cover that you'd
like to talk about for flaky tests one
of the things that I think we've not yet
talked about is the isolation that you
sometimes introduce into a testing
process when you're using something like
a virtual machine or a Docker container
often if you're not able to control the
state in a way that is appropriate it
can be helpful in my experience to
introduce extra kinds of isolation
through VMS or through containers you
can run those on your own development
workstation and you can also set it up
in CI so that at various points during
the testing process you start up a fresh
virtual machine or create a new Docker
container instance and even though
that's a little bit more costly it may
give you more confidence that flakiness
is not going to develop when you're
executing the test Suite
yeah that's a great point about the
docker container and in today's world of
kubernetes and Docker containers it also
makes it easier for you to try and
replicate your production environment
more right because you could conceivably
use the docker file and that specifies
the amount of CPU and the amount of
memory that the program would probably
be running under both in production as
well so you can kind of help you uh kind
of find your flaky test early and
potential performance issues as well if
you use the docker container as a test
Suite that's a great Point Gregory thank
you and is there anything else that you
wanted to cover
well I wanted to connect to something
you said just one moment ago one of the
things that I have found super helpful
is to actually rewrite my Docker
containers or to have multiple Docker
files that do in fact change the amount
of memory that's available
or alternatively that change how much of
a CPU is available I often run my test
cases in different kinds of Docker
containers with different types of
resource constraints because when I do
that it often helps me to identify
defects that are related to timing
issues resource issues or scheduling
issues so I think the point you made a
moment ago is a really important one to
remember we can use Docker containers to
change the execution environment and
that's critically important nice yeah so
this was a great kind of an overview and
I think we covered a lot of ground I
want to thank you Gregory for the time
and for answering these questions so
well and giving your experience and
talking about you know real world
scenarios it's quite
enlightening thank you for your time
Gregory thank you so much for inviting
me to be a guest on software engineer
hearing radio it was awesome to be able
to chat about flaky tests and I hope the
listeners of this episode will follow up
with you and me and check the material
in the show notes to learn more about
flaky test cases and some of the
solutions that we're developing both to
find and fix flaky tests absolutely yes
we will be having Gregory's contact
details his Twitter handle LinkedIn Etc
as well as links to his papers on flaky
tests and other topics that he's been
working on in the show notes thank you
once again Gregory and have a good day
thank you very much as well have a great
afternoon
[Music]
thanks for listening to SC radio an
educational program brought to you by
IEEE software magazine for more about
the podcast including other episodes
visit our website at
se.radio.net to provide feedback you can
comment on each episode on the website
or reach us on LinkedIn Facebook Twitter
or through our slack Channel at SC radio
dot slack.com you can also email us at
team sc-radio.net
this and all other episodes of SC radio
is licensed under created Commons
license 2.5
thanks for listening